Hayley Mills is at it again !
The Parent Trap II is a family, comedy, tv movie
film directed by Ronald F. Maxwell.
Two best friends plot to get their single parents together
to stop one of them from moving to New York.
Susan Corey / Sharon Ferris, played by Hayley Mills.
Bill Grand, played by Tom Skerritt.
Nikki Ferris, played by Carrie Kei Heim.
Mary Grand, played by Bridgette Andersen.
Brian Corey, played by Alex Harvey.
Florence, played by Gloria Cromwell.
The Parent Trap II is a 1986 American made-for-television comedy film and a sequel to Disney's 1961
film The Parent Trap (which was based on the 1949 book Lisa and Lottie by Erich Kästner).
It is part of the The Parent Trap series.
It premiered on the Disney Channel on July 26, 1986 as a part of
the channel’s “Hayley Mills Film Festival” banner.
Hayley Mills is the only actress that returned from the original film.
She continues to portray Susan and Sharon, the twins who were separated at age one, met up twelve years
later at summer camp, switched places and went on to reunite their divorced parents.
The film focuses on Sharon's daughter, Nikki, who tries to connect her mother
with her best friend Mary's father, portrayed by Tom Skerritt.
It was a success for the Disney Channel and it later spawned two more
made-for-television sequels, both produced in 1989.
The film explores themes of jealousy, single parent,
horseback riding, marriage, sequel.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.